Guide to the Al Swift Congressional Papers 1885-2003
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Office Files, 1979-1994; Series II
  - Personal Correspondence, 1978-1994; Subseries 12
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/82 (Box-folder 128/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/8/82 (Box-folder 128/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/18/82 (Box-folder 128/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/1-7/10, 1982 (Box-folder 128/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/11-7/20, 1982 (Box-folder 128/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/21-7/31, 1982 (Box-folder 129/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/1-8/15, 1982 (Box-folder 129/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/16-8/31, 1982 (Box-folder 129/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/82 (Box-folder 129/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/9/82 (Box-folder 129/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/16/82 (Box-folder 129/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/82 (Box-folder 129/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/82 (Box-folder 129/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/82 (Box-folder 129/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/83 (Box-folder 129/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/83 (Box-folder 129/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/83 (Box-folder 129/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/83 (Box-folder 129/13)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/83 (Box-folder 129/14)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/83 (Box-folder 129/15)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/83 (Box-folder 130/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/1/83 (Box-folder 130/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/2-8/15, 1983 (Box-folder 130/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/16-8/31, 1983 (Box-folder 130/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/1-9/15, 1983 (Box-folder 130/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/16-9/30, 1983 (Box-folder 130/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/83 (Box-folder 130/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/83 (Box-folder 130/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/1-12/15, 1983 (Box-folder 130/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/16-12/31, 1983 (Box-folder 130/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/84 (Box-folder 130/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/26/84 (Box-folder 130/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/1-2/20, 1984 (Box-folder 130/13)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/21-2/29, 1984 (Box-folder 130/14)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/1-3/15, 1984 (Box-folder 130/15)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/16-3/31, 1984 (Box-folder 130/16)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/1-4/15, 1984 (Box-folder 131/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/16-4/30, 1984 (Box-folder 131/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/1-5/15, 1984 (Box-folder 131/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/16-5/31, 1984 (Box-folder 131/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/1-6/15, 1984 (Box-folder 131/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/16-6/30, 1984 (Box-folder 131/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/84 (Box-folder 131/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/1-8/15, 1984 (Box-folder 131/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/16-8/31, 1984 (Box-folder 131/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/84 (Box-folder 131/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/84 (Box-folder 131/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/84 (Box-folder 131/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/85 (Box-folder 132/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/85 (Box-folder 132/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/1-3/10, 1985 (Box-folder 132/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/11-3/31, 1985 (Box-folder 132/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/85 (Box-folder 132/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/85 (Box-folder 132/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/85 (Box-folder 132/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/1-7/15, 1985 (Box-folder 132/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/16-7/31, 1985 (Box-folder 132/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/85 (Box-folder 132/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/85 (Box-folder 132/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/4/85 (Box-folder 132/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/30/85 (Box-folder 133/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/1-10/15, 1985 (Box-folder 133/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/16-10/31, 1985 (Box-folder 133/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/1-11/10, 1985 (Box-folder 133/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/11-11/20, 1985 (Box-folder 133/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/21-11/30, 1985 (Box-folder 133/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/85 (Box-folder 133/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/1-1/10, 1986 (Box-folder 133/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/11-1/20, 1986 (Box-folder 133/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/21-1/31, 1986 (Box-folder 133/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/1-2/20, 1986 (Box-folder 133/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/21-2/28, 1986 (Box-folder 133/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/1-3/15, 1986 (Box-folder 134/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/16-3/31, 1986 (Box-folder 134/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/1-4/15, 1986 (Box-folder 134/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/16-4/30, 1986 (Box-folder 134/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/1-5/15, 1986 (Box-folder 134/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/16-5/31, 1986 (Box-folder 134/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/1-6/15, 1986 (Box-folder 134/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/16-6/30, 1986 (Box-folder 134/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/1-7/20, 1986 (Box-folder 134/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/21-7/31, 1986 (Box-folder 134/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/1-8/10, 1986 (Box-folder 134/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/11-8/31, 1986 (Box-folder 134/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/1-9/15, 1986 (Box-folder 135/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/16-9/30, 1986 (Box-folder 135/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/1-10/15, 1986 (Box-folder 135/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/16-10/31, 1986 (Box-folder 135/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/1-11/20, 1986 (Box-folder 135/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/21-11/30, 1986 (Box-folder 135/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/86 (Box-folder 135/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/1-1/15, 1987 (Box-folder 135/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/16-1/31, 1987 (Box-folder 135/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/1-2/10, 1987 (Box-folder 135/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/11-2/19, 1987 (Box-folder 135/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/20-2/28, 1987 (Box-folder 136/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/87 (Box-folder 136/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/87 (Box-folder 136/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/9/87 (Box-folder 136/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/1-5/15, 1987 (Box-folder 136/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/16-5/31, 1987 (Box-folder 136/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/1-6/10, 1987 (Box-folder 136/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/11-6/20, 1987 (Box-folder 136/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/21-6/30, 1987 (Box-folder 136/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/1-7/15, 1987 (Box-folder 136/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/16-731, 1987 (Box-folder 136/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/87 (Box-folder 137/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/1-9/16, 1987 (Box-folder 137/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/17/87 (Box-folder 137/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/18-9/30, 1987 (Box-folder 137/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/1-10/12, 1987 (Box-folder 137/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/13/87 (Box-folder 137/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/14-10/31, 1987 (Box-folder 137/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/1-1110, 1987 (Box-folder 137/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/11-11/30, 1987 (Box-folder 137/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/1-12/15, 1987 (Box-folder 137/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/16-12/31, 1987 (Box-folder 137/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/88 (Box-folder 137/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/25/88 (Box-folder 137/13)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/1-2/10, 1988 (Box-folder 138/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/11-2/20, 1988 (Box-folder 138/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/21-2/29, 1988 (Box-folder 138/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/1-3/15, 1988 (Box-folder 138/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/16-3/31, 1988 (Box-folder 138/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/1-4/20, 1988 (Box-folder 138/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/21-4/25, 1988 (Box-folder 138/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/26-4/30, 1988 (Box-folder 138/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/1-5/20, 1988 (Box-folder 138/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/21-5/31, 1988 (Box-folder 138/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/1-6/5, 1988 (Box-folder 138/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/6-6/30, 1988 (Box-folder 138/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/88 (Box-folder 139/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/88 (Box-folder 139/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/1-9/10, 1988 (Box-folder 139/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/11-9/20, 1988 (Box-folder 139/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/21-9/30, 1988 (Box-folder 139/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/1-10/15, 1988 (Box-folder 139/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/16-10/31, 1988 (Box-folder 139/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/88 (Box-folder 139/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/88 (Box-folder 139/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/89 (Box-folder 139/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/26/89 (Box-folder 139/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/89 (Box-folder 139/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/89 (Box-folder 139/13)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/1-4/15, 1989 (Box-folder 140/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/16-4/30, 1989 (Box-folder 140/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/1-5/5, 1989 (Box-folder 140/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/6-5/16, 1989 (Box-folder 140/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/17-5/31, 1989 (Box-folder 140/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/1-6/20, 1989 (Box-folder 140/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/16-6/30, 1989 (Box-folder 140/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/89 (Box-folder 140/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/25/89 (Box-folder 140/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/89 (Box-folder 140/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/1-9/10, 1989 (Box-folder 140/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, /11-9/30, 1989 (Box-folder 140/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/20/89 (Box-folder 141/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/27/89 (Box-folder 141/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/1-10/15, 1989 (Box-folder 141/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/16-10/31, 1989 (Box-folder 141/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/89 (Box-folder 141/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/21/89 (Box-folder 141/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/22/89 (Box-folder 141/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/89 (Box-folder 141/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/13/89 (Box-folder 141/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/18/89 (Box-folder 141/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/90 (Box-folder 141/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/17/90 (Box-folder 141/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/90 (Box-folder 141/13)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/90 (Box-folder 142/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/90 (Box-folder 142/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/90 (Box-folder 142/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/90 (Box-folder 142/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/1-7/15, 1990 (Box-folder 142/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/16-7/31, 1990 (Box-folder 142/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/90 (Box-folder 142/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/90 (Box-folder 142/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/1-10/16, 1990 (Box-folder 142/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/17-10/31, 1990 (Box-folder 142/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/90 (Box-folder 142/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/90 (Box-folder 143/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/91 (Box-folder 143/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/91 (Box-folder 143/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/1-2/20, 1991 (Box-folder 143/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/21-2/28, 1991 (Box-folder 143/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/1-3/24, 1991 (Box-folder 143/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/25-3/31, 1991 (Box-folder 143/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/91 (Box-folder 143/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/91 (Box-folder 143/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/91 (Box-folder 143/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/91 (Box-folder 143/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/91 (Box-folder 143/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/91 (Box-folder 144/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/91 (Box-folder 144/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/91 (Box-folder 144/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/91 (Box-folder 144/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/92 (Box-folder 144/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/92 (Box-folder 144/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/92 (Box-folder 144/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/92 (Box-folder 144/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/92 (Box-folder 144/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/92 (Box-folder 144/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/92 (Box-folder 144/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/92 (Box-folder 144/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/92 (Box-folder 145/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/92 (Box-folder 145/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/92 (Box-folder 145/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/92 (Box-folder 145/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/93 (Box-folder 145/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/93 (Box-folder 145/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/93 (Box-folder 145/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/93 (Box-folder 145/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/93 (Box-folder 145/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/93 (Box-folder 145/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/93 (Box-folder 145/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/93 (Box-folder 145/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/7/93 (Box-folder 145/13)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/93 (Box-folder 145/14)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/93 (Box-folder 146/1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/93 (Box-folder 146/2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 12/93 (Box-folder 146/3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1/94 (Box-folder 146/4)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2/94 (Box-folder 146/5)
    - Personal Correspondence, 3/94 (Box-folder 146/6)
    - Personal Correspondence, 4/94 (Box-folder 146/7)
    - Personal Correspondence, 5/94 (Box-folder 146/8)
    - Personal Correspondence, 6/94 (Box-folder 146/9)
    - Personal Correspondence, 7/94 (Box-folder 146/10)
    - Personal Correspondence, 8/94 (Box-folder 146/11)
    - Personal Correspondence, 9/94 (Box-folder 146/12)
    - Personal Correspondence, 10/94 (Box-folder 146/13)
    - Personal Correspondence, 11/94 (Box-folder 146/14)
  - Non-District Correspondence, 1985-1994; Subseries 13
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 147/1)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1986 (Box-folder 147/2)
    - Correspondence, Jul-Oct 1986 (Box-folder 147/3)
    - Correspondence, Nov-Dec 1986 (Box-folder 147/4)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box-folder 147/5)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box-folder 147/6)
    - A, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 147/7)
    - B, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 147/8)
    - B, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 147/9)
    - B, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/1)
    - C, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/2)
    - C, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/3)
    - D, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/4)
    - E, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/5)
    - F, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/6)
    - G, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/7)
    - H, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/8)
    - I, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/9)
    - J, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/10)
    - K, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 148/11)
    - L, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/1)
    - Mc, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/2)
    - M, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/3)
    - N, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/4)
    - O, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/5)
    - P, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/6)
    - R, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/7)
    - S, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/8)
    - S, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 149/9)
    - T, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 150/1)
    - U, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 150/2)
    - V, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 150/3)
    - W, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 150/4)
    - Y, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 150/5)
    - Z, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 150/6)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box-folder 150/7)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 150/8)
    - Correspondence, Jan-May 1993 (Box-folder 150/9)
    - Correspondence, Jun-Dec 1993 (Box-folder 150/10)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 150/11)
  - Form Letters (Deleted), 1979-1994; Subseries 14
    - Letters, Aug. 27, 1979 (Box-folder 151/1)
    - Letters, Aug. 28, 1979 (Box-folder 151/2)
    - Letters, Aug. 29, 1979 (Box-folder 151/3)
    - Letters, Feb. 27, 1980 (Box-folder 151/4)
    - Abortion (Anti), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/5)
    - Abortion (Pro-Choice), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/6)
    - Academy Nominations, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/7)
    - Alaska Lands, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/8)
    - All American Pipeline, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/9)
    - Amtrak Cuts, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/10)
    - Appointment as page, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/11)
    - Balanced Budget, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/12)
    - Call Do Follow-up, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/13)
    - Campaign Financing (H.R. 1), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/14)
    - Carry Over Basis Follow-Up, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/15)
    - Case Follow-Up, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/16)
    - Chrysler Assistance (Federal Bail-Out), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/17)
    - Club, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/18)
    - Customs (Blaine Border), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/19)
    - Dairy Follow-up, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/20)
    - Davis-Bacon Act, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/21)
    - Dept. of Education (H.R. 2444), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/22)
    - The Draft, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/23)
    - Energy, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/24)
    - Federal Retirement/Social Security, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/25)
    - Federal Spending Limitation Amendment, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/26)
    - Food Stamps, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/27)
    - Form Tapes (Xerox)- Listing, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151/28)
    - High Interest and State Usury Limit (H.R. 4986 et.al.), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/1)
    - High Interest and State Usury Limit (H.R. 4986 et.al.), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/2)
    - Hospital Cost Containment, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/3)
    - H.R. 777, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/4)
    - H.R. 3333 Communications Bill, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/5)
    - Inflation/Balanced Budget (Cost of Living), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/6)
    - Iron, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/7)
    - IRS Tax on Schools, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/8)
    - Listening Post/Case Follow-up, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/9)
    - Listening Post Follow-up, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/10)
    - Middle East Peace Treaty, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/11)
    - Military Cost of Living, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/12)
    - Milwaukee Railroad, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/13)
    - Mottle Amend. (Pro) H.Res. 74, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/14)
    - National Federation of Independent Business (NFIB) Reports, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/15)
    - National Federation of Independent Business (NFIB) Reports, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/16)
    - New Citizen Letter, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/17)
    - Northern Tier, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/18)
    - Nuclear Power, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/19)
    - Nutrition Program for Elderly (Meals on Wheels), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/20)
    - Obey- Railsback, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/21)
    - Panama Canal, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/22)
    - Personal Savings Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/23)
    - Prayer in Schools, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/24)
    - Rare II, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/25)
    - Refugees (Boat People), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/26)
    - Regional Power, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/27)
    - S.A.L.T. II Treaties, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/28)
    - Senior Citizens, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 152/29)
    - Share Draft (Interest), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/1)
    - Share Draft Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/2)
    - Skagit Nuke, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/3)
    - Stop In Do Follow Up, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/4)
    - Sunset Laws- NFIB, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/5)
    - Susan B. Anthony One Dollar Coin, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/6)
    - Toll Free Follow-Up, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/7)
    - Trucking Deregulation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/8)
    - Value Added Tax, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/9)
    - Wage and Price Controls, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/10)
    - Withholding Tax on Interest and Dividends, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/11)
    - World Peace Tax Fund, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/12)
    - Youth, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 153/13)
    - #1-6300, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 153/14)
    - #6301-10000, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 153/15)
    - #10001-12350, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 153/16)
    - #12351-14000, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 153/17)
    - #14001-17100, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 153/18)
    - #17101-18200, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 154/1)
    - #18201-19000, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 154/2)
    - #19001-28000, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 154/3)
    - #28001-28700, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 154/4)
    - #28701-28908, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 154/5)
    - #1-1250, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 154/6)
    - #1251-7000, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 154/7)
    - #7001-13000, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 154/8)
    - #13001-16000, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 154/9)
    - #16001-17200, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 155/1)
    - #17201-18000, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 155/2)
    - #18001-19000, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 155/3)
    - #19001-28400, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 155/4)
    - #28401-28655, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 155/5)
    - #28656-28900, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 155/6)
    - 99th Congress, 1985 (Box-folder 155/7)
    - 99th Congress, 1985 (Box-folder 155/8)
    - 99th Congress, 1985 (Box-folder 155/9)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 156/1)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 156/2)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 156/3)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 156/4)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 156/5)
    - 99th Congress, 1986 (Box-folder 156/6)
    - Follow ups, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 157/1)
    - Follow ups, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 157/2)
    - Follow ups, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 157/3)
    - Follow ups, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 157/4)
    - Follow ups, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 157/5)
    - Follow ups, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 157/6)
    - Follow ups, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 157/7)
    - Follow ups, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 157/8)
    - Follow ups, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 157/9)
  - Awards, Plaques and Artifacts, 1979-1991; Subseries 15
    - Realtor Award: "Affordable Housing", Undated (Box 158)
    - Award: Independent Baker Assoc., 1994 (Box 158)
    - Award: Superfund Reauthorization Fund, Undated (Box 158)
    - Special Commendation Award: Clallam County, 1992 (Box 158)
    - Plaque: PACE Project--U.S. PACE Team, Undated (Box 158)
    - Certificate of Appreciation: Washington State POW/MIA Concerned Citizens Assoc."Government Official 50th Anniversary Award": American Electronics Assoc., 1993 (Box 158)
    - Certificate of Appreciation: Japanese American Citizens League, 1988 (Box 158)
    - Award: Stevens Middle School--Port Angeles, WA, Oct 26, 1988 (Box 158)
    - Broadcasting Article (Framed), Jan 21, 1980 (Box 158)
    - Certificate of Merit: American Bar Association of Whatcom County, 1974 (Box 159)
    - Award: "Alligator Clip", Undated (Box 159)
    - Award: Department of Defense--Federal Voting Assistance Program, Undated (Box 159)
    - Plaque: P.H.A.D.A., Sept. 1994 (Box 159)
    - Plaque: Clallam County Democrats, Undated (Box 159)
    - Plaque: U.S. House of Representatives--Administrative Assistants Assoc., 1987 (Box 159)
    - Plaque: National Treasury Employees Union Chapter 30, Seattle--In Appreciation..., Undated (Box 159)
    - Plaque: Congressional Fire Services Institute, 1991 (Box 159)
    - Plaque: Air and Water Technologies--Acid Rain Seminar, Undated (Box 159)
    - Award: Jefferson County Democrats, 1986 (Box 159)
    - Plaque: National Energy Resources Organization, 1993 (Box 159)
    - Plaque: John Wayne Marina Dedication, Undated (Box 159)
    - Plaque: Save NAS Whidbey Task Force, 1991 (Box 159)
    - Embroidery: "What is the Nation Yearning For, A Good Democrat: Al Swift", Undated (Box 159)
    - Award: National Federation of Independent Business--Guardian of Small Business Hon. Allan Byron Swift 99th Congress, Undated (Box 160)